<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trusted IoT</title>
    <link>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Trusted IoT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 22:02:58 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deliverables</title>
      <link>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/deliverables/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:52:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/deliverables/</guid>
      <description>Deliverables in WP1 D1.1 (M6, M12, M18, M24): Reports of Meetings and Discussions. Deliverables in WP2 D2.1 (M3): Requirements Specification for the Use Cases. (pdf) This deliverable contains the technical, functional and security related requirements for each use case. D2.2 (M3): Specification of the Architectural Framework. (pdf) This deliverable includes the overall framework architecture to define the different components, which meet these requirements and define the intercommunication among these components in order to address all the requirements in an integrated way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning</title>
      <link>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 22:39:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/planning/</guid>
      <description>A Gantt-chart of the planning in Trusted IoT can be seen below. The project started on September 1st, 2022.
WP 1: Project Management D 1.1 (M1): Reports of Meetings and Discussions WP 2: Exploration, Specification &amp;amp; Requirements study WP 3: Platform-specific security solutions WP 4: Industrial Use Case Demonstration WP 5: Dissemination and Exploitation M 5.1 (M3): Kick-off meeting + project website the kick-off meeting took place on Septebmer 15, 2022 in Brussels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Partners</title>
      <link>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 22:21:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/partners/</guid>
      <description>In Trusted IoT, the research is conducted by 5 parters from Belgium and Germany.
Belgian Partners Vrije Universiteit Brussel (VUB) Name of research group
An Braeken, Laurent Segers, Bruno da Silva, and Abdellah Touhafi
KU Leuven Emerging technologies, Systems and Security (ES&amp;amp;S)
Nele Mentens, Masoom Rabbani and Jo Vliegen
German Partners Universität Rostock Forschungsgebiete Integrierte Systeme
Marc Reichenbach and Johannes Knödtel
Technische Universität Dresden Adaptive Dynamic systems
Diana Göhringer and Sergio Pertuz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 11:52:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jvliegen.github.io/trusted_iot_website/presentations/</guid>
      <description>Closing meeting (invite) August 29th 2024, Berlin (hybrid) Slides of KU Leuven (slides pdf) The seconds Intermediate User Group meetings Belgian meeting - April 17th 2024, Brussels (hybrid) Slides of General presentation (slides pdf) Slides of ARC presentation (slides pdf) Slides of Progress VUB (slides pdf) Slides of KU Leuven (slides pdf, video of demonstrator youtube) Meeting minutes (pdf) German meeting - April 16th 2024, Rostock (hybrid) Slides of General presentation (slides pdf) Slides of Progress TUD (slides pdf) Slides of Progress URO (slides pdf) The Dissemination event - IIoTSBOM - November 16th 2023, Leuven Slides of TUD (slides pdf) Slides of UOR (slides pdf) Slides of GFai (slides pdf) Slides of KUL (slides pdf) Slides of VUB (slides pdf) The first Intermediate User Group meetings German meeting - June 20th 2023, Dresden Belgian meeting - June 9th 2023, Diepenbeek Slides of General presentation (slides pdf) Slides of Progress VUB (slides pdf) Slides of KU Leuven (slides pdf, video of demonstrator youtube) Meeting minutes (pdf) The Kick-off meetings German meeting - December 1st 2022, Berlin Belgian meeting - December 2nd 2022, Brussels Slides of Introduction (here) Slides of Embedded security + VUB use cases (here, and here) Slides of RISC-V + KU Leuven use case (here) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
